<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>location on MR MiniApp</title>
    <link>http://tonniz.github.io/docs/api/%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/</link>
    <description>Recent content in location on MR MiniApp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://tonniz.github.io/docs/api/%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://tonniz.github.io/docs/api/%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/%E5%9C%B0%E5%9B%BE%E7%BB%84%E4%BB%B6%E6%8E%A7%E5%88%B6/map/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tonniz.github.io/docs/api/%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/%E5%9C%B0%E5%9B%BE%E7%BB%84%E4%BB%B6%E6%8E%A7%E5%88%B6/map/</guid>
      <description>uni.createMapContext(mapId,this)#Creates and returns a map context mapContextobject. In the custom component, the second component parameters into the this example, the operation to the component &amp;lt;map&amp;gt;assembly.
List of methods of the mapContext object
   method parameter Description     getCenterLocation OBJECT Get the latitude and longitude of the current map center, the return is the gcj02 coordinate system   moveToLocation OBJECT To move the center of the map to the current location, it needs to be used with the show-location of the map component   getRegion OBJECT Get the field of view of the current map   getScale OBJECT Get the zoom level of the current map    $getAppMap() Precautions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://tonniz.github.io/docs/api/%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/%E6%9F%A5%E7%9C%8B%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/open-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tonniz.github.io/docs/api/%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/%E6%9F%A5%E7%9C%8B%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/open-location/</guid>
      <description>uni.openLocation(OBJECT)#Use the in-app map to view the location.
OBJECT parameter description
   parameter name Types Required Description Platform difference description     latitude Float Yes Latitude, the range is -90~90, a negative number means south latitude, using the gcj02 National Survey    longitude Float Yes Longitude, the range is -180~180, the negative number indicates the west longitude, using the gcj02 National Survey    success Function no Callback function for successful interface call    fail Function no Callback function for interface call failure    complete Function no The callback function for the end of the interface call (the call will be executed if it succeeds or fails)     Example</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://tonniz.github.io/docs/api/%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/%E8%8E%B7%E5%8F%96%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tonniz.github.io/docs/api/%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/%E8%8E%B7%E5%8F%96%E4%BD%8D%E7%BD%AE/location/</guid>
      <description>uni.getLocation(OBJECT)#Get the current geographic location and speed.
In the WeChat Mini Program, after the user leaves the application, this interface cannot be called unless the background continuous positioning permission is requested; when the user clicks &amp;ldquo;display at the top of the chat&amp;rdquo;, this interface can continue to be called.
OBJECT parameter description
   parameter name Types Required Description     type String no The default is wgs84 return gps coordinates, gcj02 return to the country office coordinate measurement can be used to uni.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
